太好了，大家都在
-Good! You guys are all here.
怎么了？
-What's up?
我明天要去罗夫罗兰面试
I have a job interview at Ralph Lauren tomorrow.
恭喜，太棒了… 我知道
Congratulations!
那个牌子的内裤逊毙了
Oh,boy. That guy's underwear sucks!
什么？
-What?
我买了一条超小号的内裤 （与excess“多余的”同音）
-Well,I got this pair marked "XS."
里头根本塞不下多余的东西
Let me tell you,there was no room for excess anything in there.
反正工作是女装部的联络人 我直接在主管底下做事
I'll be the coordinator of the women's collection.I'll work right under the director.
这是我梦寐以求的工作
It's the perfect job for me!
如果你通过面试就成了 是啊
If you nail the interview,you'll get it.
要不要练习一下面试技巧？
You want to work on your interview skills?
好啊 好耶
Okay!
来，先从握手开始
Let's start with the handshake.
嗨 嗨
Hi
很会握，手腕的动作很棒
Very good handshake. Good wrist action.
我来试试 好
Let me try.Okay
天啊！我哪里得罪你了？
Oh,my God! What did I ever do to you?
我握得太用力？
Did I squeeze too hard?
这么说吧，好在我不是钱德
Let's just say I'm glad I'm not Chandler.
本集播出：“瑞秋的面试之吻”
The One with Rachel's lnadvertent Kiss
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
罗斯，我能看到你在新公寓
That's right,Ross. I can see you in your new apartment.
你也看得到我
You can see me
跟昨天一样…跟前天也一样
Same as yesterday,same as the day before.
他开始演鲨鱼攻击了没？
Is he doing his "shark attack" bit?
还没…等等，他开始了
No. Oh,wait! There he goes.
罗斯，很好笑
Very funny,Ross.
栩栩如生又好笑
Very lifelike and funny.
不…小姐，我不是向你挥手
No,no. I wasn't waving at you,lady.
或许我是喔
Whoa,maybe I was.
莫妮卡，罗斯那栋楼里 有个辣妹在勾引我
This hot girl in Ross' building is flirting with me.
你去啊，勾引回来，瞎搅和
Get in there,man. Flirt back. Mix it up!
我知道啦
Yeah,I'm down with that.
好，来咯
Okay,here goes.
你…
How...
好…
...you...
不好？
...doing?
有用耶，她挥手要我过去
It worked! She's waving me over.
好，我马上过去
I'll be right over.
我看看，她住在三楼…
Let's see,she's on the third floor....
她真的很美耶
-She is pretty,huh?
这还用你说
-Tell me about it.
不…我跟她没关系 她只是莫妮卡
No,no! I'm not with her.That's just Monica.
乔伊，我很会演吧？
Hey,Joey!Great stuff,huh?
这是你家？ 当然是
This your place?Yeah,of course it is.
请进
Come on in.
对了，经过窗户能假装在冲浪
Go by the window. You can pretend to be surfing.
可是我算过啊 这里住的不应该是你
I counted. You're not supposed to live here!
要命！
Oh,man!
怎么了？
What happened?
我最后跑到罗斯家去了 一定是我算错了
I ended up at Ross' place. I must have miscounted or something.
可恶，她不在了
Damn! She's not there anymore.
你看，罗斯在演看电视那段
Look,Ross is doing his "watching TV" bit.
乔伊，我觉得他真的在看电视
No,Joe,I think he's just watching TV.
嫌犯已失去踪迹
We've lost visual contact with the suspect.
好，我现在非走不可了
Okay,now I really have to go.
这真是太不公平了
It's so unfair
有人开枪打店员 我们的约会就得中断
that our date has to get cut short...just because some guy shot at a store clerk.
亲爱的，我知道 但这是我的工作
-I know,but it's my job.
好吧，不如我一起去
-Then maybe I could come too
嫌犯刚从水沟中裸体现身
Suspect has just emerged naked from the sewer.
好吧，你去就好
All right,you go.
再见 好，再见
Bye Bye！Okay！Bye
天啊 怎么了？
-Oh,God! -What?
我好想念他
Oh,I just miss him so much!
才一个星期就这么亲密了
For just a week,you guys are close.
是啊，说来很奇怪
Yeah,it's weird.
可是我没办法，他真的很体贴
I can't help it. He's so sweet.
像是小狗狗，却很强悍 还会开枪打坏人
He's like this little puppy dog,you know?But like a really tough one who shoots bad guys.
我最喜欢刚开始恋爱的感觉
I love the beginning parts of relationships.
彼此难分难舍
You can't keep your hands off each other.
我知道，热恋是最棒的
I know. It is the best.
你和钱德的热恋持续了多久？
How long did that last for you and Chandler?
什么？我们还在热恋啊
What? It's still going on.
少来，老实说，何时结束的？
Come on,seriously. When did it end?
我是很老实啊 我们一直粘在一起
I am serious. We're all over each other all the time.
好吧，你们的事你最清楚 我只是好奇罢了
Okay,you know where you are better than I do.
菲比，你别发神经了好不好？
Why don't you just calm down?
请你先去把事实搞清楚
Get all your facts
不要逢人便说 全天下只有你们在热恋！
before you tell everybody you're the only hot couple.
天啊，野兽被我吵醒了
God,I woke the beast.
显然是我错了，我失言
I was wrong,obviously. I just misspoke.
没事了 没事了
It's okay. It is okay.
只要你知道我和钱德 也和你们一样火热缠绵就好
As long as you know Chandler and l are also hot and fiery.Just as hot as you.
我们的热情…正在燃烧
I mean,our flame....It is on fire!
莫妮卡，扫把还你
Here's your broom back.
你真可爱
You are so cute!
她想把我的可爱全吸过去
The cute bar keeps getting lower and lower,doesn't it?
面试顺不顺利？
How'd the interview go?
糟透了，我犯了最蠢 最丢人的错误
Horrible! I did the stupidest,most embarrassing thing.
你跟考官说要跟他老婆上床 然后又从椅子上跌下来？
Did you say you wanted to have sex with his wife then fall off your chair?
不是
No
你在面试之前喝醉了？
Did you get drunk on the way over there?
不是
No
难怪你没说要跟他老婆上床
Well,that explains why you didn't do the other stuff.
那是怎么了？
So,what happened?
真是糟糕透顶 原本面试都很顺利
It was horrible! And the interview part went so well.
我还把大家逗笑了
I even made him laugh.
考官说到什么船的事
He said something about a boat...
我答腔说 “只要救生衣够多就行”
...and I was like,"Well,yeah,if you've got enough life jackets."
相信我，当时真的很逗
Trust me. It was actually very funny.
反正到了最后说再见…
Anyway,we were saying goodbye and....
怎么了？
What happened?
我们当时正要握手 他缓缓朝我靠过来
We were shaking hands...and he leaned in toward me.
他也许是要帮我开门 但是我完全误会了
Maybe he was opening the door...but I totally misread him
所以我就…
and I....
你亲了上去？
You kissed him?
我又没有别的办法
I didn't know what else to do!
你可以试着…
You could have tried...
别去亲他 钱德，真是多谢你
...not kissing him.Thanks,Chandler.
瑞秋，罗夫罗兰的人来电 要你去第二关面试
A guy from Ralph Lauren called. You got a second interview.
莫妮卡，这并不好笑
Monica,that's not funny.
那好吧
Oh,okay.
罗夫罗兰的人来电 要你去第二关面试
A guy from Ralph Lauren called You got a second interview
莫妮卡，你最好认真一点
Oh,my God,Monica,you better be serious.
刚才是你要我搞笑的
You just told me to be funny!
不敢相信我还能去第二关面试
Oh,my God. I can't believe it! I got a second interview.
我看那一吻没那么糟嘛
That kiss isn't looking like such a mistake now,is it?
慢着…他要我回去面试 不是因为那一吻吧？
You don't think that's why he wants me back?
是啊…
Yeah!
不是
No?
你们在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我意外地在面试中亲了考官 他现在还要我回去
I accidentally kissed him in the interview...and now he wants me back
“把那逢人便亲的女孩带来”
...because,"Let's bring back the girl who kisses everybody!"
瑞秋，你别乱想了
Come on,Rach.
天啊，万一他觉得我是那种 随便跟他上床的人怎么办？
What if he thinks I'll just sleep with him?
他要你回去面试 或许是因为你适合那工作
He wants you back because you're right for the job.
或许吧，我不知道…
Maybe. I don't know.
天啊，我怎么会那么蠢？
Oh,God! How could I be so stupid?
瑞秋，快别那样说了 乔伊给你个抱抱就好
Rachel,don't say that. I think you just need a hug from Joey.
来…
Come on. Come on.
她回来了！辣妹回来了！
She's back! Hot girl's back!
还不完全是，但是谢谢你
Well,I'm not totally back yet,but I appreciate it.
不是说你，是罗斯那栋楼的辣妹 她回来了…
No. In Ross' building. She's back!
等一下，我马上过去
Wait there. I'll be over in a second.
一、二、三…知道了
One,two,three.... Got it!
我来看看她有多辣
I gotta check out this hot girl.
辣妹在这里
There she is!
可恶，你搬家啦！
Damn it! Did you move?
是啊，我跟你们住了一阵子 然后搬到了这里
Yes.I lived with you for a while. Then I found this place.
我是罗斯
I'm Ross.
有什么事？
Yes？
你家里有住辣妹吗？
Do you happen to have a hot girl in there?
没有，我一个人住
No,I'm all alone.
是啊，我很遗憾
Yeah. Sorry about that.
小女孩，你好
Hey,little girl.
你妈妈、姐姐或是保姆 有没有谁正好是辣妹？
Is your mommy or sister or babysitter,by any chance,a hot girl?
爹地！
-Daddy!
下次再聊
-Later,girl!
真要命
Oh,man!
辣妹！
Hot girl?
辣妹…
Hot girl!
瑞秋，请进
Hi,Rachel. Come on in.
很高兴再次见到你 谢谢
-It's nice to see you again. -Thank you.
瑞秋…
Rachel…
什么？
What?
你说什么？
-Excuse me?
我来帮你…
-Yeah,let me
好，我知道是怎么回事了
Okay,I see what's going on here.
听着，抱歉让你误会了
Now,look...I'm sorry if I gave you the wrong impression.
但我不是那种随便的女孩 为了工作就能出卖肉体
But I am not some hussy who will just sleep around to get ahead.
听我说！ …虽然我亲过你
Even though I kissed you,that does not give you...
你也没有权利要我跟你上床
...the right to demand sex from me!
这份工作我也没有那么想要
I do not want this job that bad.
再会
Good day,sir.
进去见则纳先生 可得准备好卖弄风骚
If you're going in there to see Mr. Zelner,I hope you're ready to put out.
我会的
I am.
说了你们一定不信 罗夫罗兰那杂碎对我做了什么
You are not gonna believe...what that sleazeball from Ralph Lauren did to me!
不可思议，你们怎么知道？
Okay,that's amazing! How did you know that?
你嘴唇上沾到墨水
You got ink on your lip.
“中央咖啡馆”
改天让我拿拿你的枪如何？
What do you say,maybe,sometime I hold your gun?
不知道，照理说不能那样
We're not supposed to do that.
又不会怎样，我的意思是…
What could happen? I mean
我看答案是不行
Yeah. I'm gonna say no.
菲比，晚餐后要去看电影吗？
-Do you want to see a movie tonight?
不行，我们已经有计划了
-We can't. We already have plans.
你们要去干嘛？
What are you doing?
就跟每天一样啊 腻在盖瑞的公寓里
Well,same thing we did all day. Just hang out at Gary's apartment.
他好厉害，我们没离开过卧房
He is so amazing. We never left the bedroom.
祝你们看电影愉快
But have fun at the movie.
我们不是要去看电影
Well,we're not seeing a movie.
那你干嘛问我们要不要去？
Then why did you ask us if we wanted to go?
我是怕你不小心冲进我房间 因为我和钱德会做上一整晚
Because I just wanted to know what you were doing...so you wouldn't walk in on me and Chandler while we were doing it all night.
失陪一下 好
Will you excuse me?
钱德，方便私下说几句话吗？ 好
Chandler? Can I see you for a second?
我们一定要打败他们
-We have got to beat them!
为什么？
-Why?
因为盖瑞和菲比 觉得他们比我们还火热
Because Gary and Phoebe think they're a hotter couple than us.
所以呢？
So?
所以我们上楼去大干一场 证明他们是错的
So we've gotta go have a lot of sex and prove them wrong!
莫妮卡，你别再比来比去 这真是疯了
You've got to stop this competitive thing. It's crazy.
只为了让盖瑞和菲比难看 我们就要上楼大战数十回合
Just to impress them,you want us to have sex over and over...
我为什么要拒绝呢？ 快去拿外套
...and I'm saying no to this,why? Get your coat!
“向我招手的辣妹 请联络乔伊”
借过
Excuse me.
“警告：有人侵入本大楼 发现这名变态请报警”
你们应该看一看 通知其他的住户
You should check this out. Tell the other tenants.
这家伙一直在找什么辣妹的
Apparently,he's looking for some kind of hot girl.
谁不是呢？
Who isn't?
我们可能还没见过，我是罗斯
I don't think we've met. I'm Ross.
我知道，你就是那个 不愿意分担工友欢送费的人
I know. You're the guy who wouldn't chip in for the handyman.
算了
Never mind.
其实我觉得大家的反应不公平 因为你才刚搬进来而已
I actually thought it was unfair the way everyone reacted.I mean,you had just moved in
没错，我刚搬进来而已，谢谢
I had just moved in!Thank you!
等等… 我是珍
Listen....Jen
珍，这听来可能有点…
Jen.I know this may sound a little
不如哪天一起喝杯咖啡？
But would you want to grab a cup of coffee sometime?
当然，没问题
Sure,that would be nice.
上面有我的电话，打给我
My number's on there. Give me a call.
我一定打
I will give you a call.
后会有期 好
-I'll see you later. -Okay.
我忘记拿报纸
I forgot my paper.
刚才真是太棒了
That was amazing.
等到吃晚餐的时候 我一定要说给菲比和盖瑞听
Phoebe and Gary are so gonna hear about this at dinner.
刚才真是太棒了
That was amazing.
我们才是热恋第一名
We are the hottest,huh?
没人比我们更热恋
No one is hotter than we are.
我们是最棒的
-We're the best.
不，最棒的是你
-No,you're the best.
不，你才是 不，你才是
-No,you're the best.-No，you're the best
我是最棒的
I am the best.
两位
Hey,guys.
你们刚才在干嘛啊？
What you been doing?
乔伊，那不是前几天跟你挥手的女孩吗？
Isn't that the girl who waved at you?
不知道，但你的床单是透明的
I don't know,but I can see through your sheet.
对，是她没错
Yeah,that's her.
不过算了吧，我无缘跟她见面
You know,it doesn't matter. I'll never meet her.
为什么？ 因为我找不到她的公寓
Why？It's impossible to find her apartment!
她就像是住在辣妹平行宇宙里
She lives in some hot-girl parallel universe or something.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
她明明就住在二楼 左边数过来第七间
She lives on the 2nd floor,7th apartment from the left.
不不不…
No,
她住在三楼 左边数过来第八间
she lives on the 3rd floor,8th apartment from the left.
不，前两个窗户是大厅的
No. Those first two windows,that's the lobby.
过去那边的是楼梯间窗户 你算错了
That other window is the stairway. You've been counting wrong.
我之前不知道 莫妮卡，感谢你
I did not know that! Thank you,Monica.
不敢相信我因为算数 差点就失去了另一个女孩
I almost lost another girl because of counting!
你准备好了吗？
-So you ready?
好了，我去拿外套 好
-Yeah,I'll just get my coat.-Okay
你能帮去我开门吗？
-Could you get that?
没问题
-Sure.
乔伊…
Joey
不！…
No! No!
首先我要谢谢你 同意再次见我
First,I would like to say thank you for seeing me again.
不要紧，但我有义务告诉你 这次的面试有录影存证
That's quite right.But I feel obligated to tell you that this meeting is being videotaped.
好，首先我要向你道歉 我不小心亲了你
Well,first,I would like to start by apologizing for kissing you...
还有对你大吼的那件事
...and for yelling at you.
很合理
Fair enough.
你或许会想要雇用不曾…
Now,you're probably going to hire one of the people who did not...
对你大吼或是夺门而出的人
yell at you and storm out.
不过那样可就错大了 原因是这样的
And I think that's a big mistake. And here's why.
我大出洋相之后还敢回来 这显示我有勇气
I made a huge fool of myself,and I came back. That shows courage.
我以为你要我用性来交换工作 当时我拒绝了
When I thought you wanted sex in exchange for this job,I said no.
这表示我有骨气
That shows integrity.
我不害怕挺身为自己辩护 这表示我有勇气
And I was not afraid to stand up for myself...and that shows courage.
我知道我已经说过勇气了
Now,I know that I've already said courage...
不过勇气总是多多益善嘛
...but you've got to have courage.
最后当我以为你 想趁工作之便占我便宜
And finally,when I thought you were making sexual advances...
我拒绝了，但是没打算告你
...I said no,and I was not litigious.
所以你看，我有勇气、有骨气
So there you go! You got courage...you got integrity
双重勇气，而且又不告你
...you got courage again...and not litigious.
那个…
Look,Mr....
则纳 对，则纳…我知道
Zelner.-Ya，Zelner，Oh,I knew that.
我真的很想要这份工作
I really,really want this job.
我想我一定会做得很好
And I think I would be really good at it.
这样吧…
You know what?
虽然我可能会后悔
I may regret this...
但我让你试试看
...but I'll give you a shot.
真的？
You are? Really?
谢谢你…
Thank you. Oh,God!
我现在抱你会不会很不得体？
Would it be inappropriate if I gave you a hug?
会 那好吧
Yes -All right
握手可以吗？
Well,how about a handshake?
天啊，对不起…
Oh,God! I'm sorry!
我不是故意要摸那个的
I did not mean to touch that!
我是说你…那里
I mean,you!There!
好了，谢谢你，我先离开
I'm gonna leave.
非常感谢…
Thank you very much.
那就星期一见咯
Hey,I'll see you Monday.
钱德，你累了？
Are you tired?
今天疯成那样，他不累才怪
You better believe he's tired after the day we had!
如果你们懂的话
If you know what I mean.
你们懂吧？
Do you know what I mean?
亲爱的，连墨西哥脆片都懂
Honey,the tortilla chips know what you mean.
钱德，我给你的警徽还喜欢吗
Do you like that badge I got you?
喜欢，很酷
Oh,yeah,it's so cool.
宾警官得要先行告退 执行10一100勤务
Now,I gotta go. Officer Bing's got a 10-100.
去尿尿
That's pee-pee.
菲比，你头发里有树枝
Phoebe,you have a twig in your hair.
来这里的路上 我们绕了一点路
We kind of took a detour on our way over here.
对，我们去公园里散步 看四下无人就…
We were strolling through the park and no one was around,so....
不会吧？ 真的有
-You didn't. -We did!
我们违反了犯罪条例 第12条第7款
We violated section 12,paragraph 7 of the criminal code.
在公园是吧？
The park,huh?
公共场所
Public place.
了解了
I hear you.
失陪一下
Can you excuse me for a second?
钱德
Hi,Chandler.
莫妮卡，这是男厕
Monica,this is the men's room.
没错吧？
Isn't it?
没错
Yes,it is.
我一直都觉得男厕很性感
I've always found the men's bathroom very sexual.
你不觉得吗？
Haven't you?
不觉得
No.
否则我们就不会在一起了
And if I did,I don't think we'd be going out.
莫妮卡，我不想让你失望
Okay,I don't want to disappoint you...
也不想让第二间那位男士失望
...and I really don't want to disappoint the guy in the second stall....
不好意思，先生
Sorry,man.
拜托，太离谱了
But come on,this is getting ridiculous.
别这样，我们不能让他们赢
Come on,we can't let them win!
我们已经证明我们在热恋了 为何你这么在乎？
We've proved that we are hot,okay? So why are you obsessed about this?
因为菲比和盖瑞不仅难分难舍 还在公园里做了那档事
Phoebe and Gary are in that..."can't keep their hands off each other" phase!
所以呢？
So?
所以我很伤心 因为我们激情不再
It makes me really sad that we're not really there anymore.
原来是为了这档事？
Oh,is that what this has all been about?
我们成天腻在一起不是比较让人兴奋吗？
Wasn't it a lot more exciting when we were...all over each other all the time?
那时很棒，真的很棒
Yeah,that was great. That was really great.
但是老实跟你说 我们现在的状况让我更兴奋
But the truth is,I'm more excited about where we are now.
真的？ 是啊
-Really? -Yeah.
我从没谈过这么久的恋爱
I've never been in a relationship this long before.
过了刚开始的激情期 还想跟对方相处在一起
To get past the beginning and still want to be around each other...
我觉得这是很不凡的
...I think that's incredible.
而且还是和你在一起
And the fact that this is happening with you...
这让我很兴奋
...I think that's pretty exciting.
真甜蜜
That's so sweet.
我知道我表现得有点过火 但是我的感觉跟你一样
I know that I was acting a little crazy...but I feel the same way.
真的？
Really？
你知道我刚领悟到什么吗？
You know what I just realized?
我们的关系让你反常 才没有
You just freaked out about our relationship.-I did not.
就是有，承认吧，你很反常
-Yes,you did!Admit it. You freaked out!
好啦，我是有一点反常
I freaked out a little.
岂止有一点，你超级反常的！
A little? You freaked out bigtime,okay?
我反败为胜，我们角色互换了
And I fixed it! We have switched places.
我现在是国王 你是搞砸又发疯的输家
I am the relationship king,and you are the crazy,irrational screwup!
现在又回到原位了
And now we're back.
没想到罗斯还真的相信
I cannot believe Ross is buying this.
谢天谢地，我再也看不下去了
Thank God! I can't watch him anymore.
你们准备好了吗？ 好了
You guys ready?-Yes
对了，多谢你把 潘蜜拉和杰丝敏（《海滩游侠》的主演）借给我们
By the way,thank you for loaning us Pamela and Yasmine.
要命，她们还真是看不腻
Man,they cannot get enough!